[{
	"name":"Airport Codes",
	"description":"This quiz covers Airport Codes.",
	"resources" : [{
		"name" : "",
		"description" : "",
		"link" : ""
	}],
	"questions": [
        {
            "question": "ABQ",
            "answer": "Albuquerque",
            "hint": "near mexico",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "ACV",
            "answer": "Eureka",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "ADK",
            "answer": "Adak Island",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "ADQ",
            "answer": "Kodiak",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "AKN",
            "answer": "King Salmon",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "ALW",
            "answer": "Walla Walla",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "ANC",
            "answer": "Anchorage",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "ATL",
            "answer": "Atlanta",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "AUS",
            "answer": "Austin",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "BET",
            "answer": "Bethel",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "BIL",
            "answer": "Billings",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "BLI",
            "answer": "Bellingham",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "BNA",
            "answer": "Nashville",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "BOI",
            "answer": "Boise",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "BOS",
            "answer": "Boston",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "BRW",
            "answer": "Barrow",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "BUR",
            "answer": "Burbank",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "BWI",
            "answer": "Baltimore",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "BZN",
            "answer": "Bozeman",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "CDV",
            "answer": "Cordova",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "CHS",
            "answer": "Charleston",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "COS",
            "answer": "Colorado Springs",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "CUN",
            "answer": "Cancun",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "DCA",
            "answer": "Washington - Reagan",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "DEN",
            "answer": "Denver",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "DFW",
            "answer": "Dallas",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "DIL",
            "answer": "Dillingham",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "DTW",
            "answer": "Detroit",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "DUT",
            "answer": "Dutch Harbor",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "EAT",
            "answer": "Wenatchee",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "EUG",
            "answer": "Eugene",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "EWR",
            "answer": "New York - Newark",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "FAI",
            "answer": "Fairbanks",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "FAT",
            "answer": "Fresno",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "FCA",
            "answer": "Kalispell",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "FLG",
            "answer": "Flagstaff",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "FLL",
            "answer": "Ft Lauderdale",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "GDL",
            "answer": "Guadalajara",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "GEG",
            "answer": "Spokane",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "GST",
            "answer": "Glacier Bay",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "GST",
            "answer": "Gustavus",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "GTF",
            "answer": "Great Falls",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "GUC",
            "answer": "Gunnison County / Crested Butte",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "HDN",
            "answer": "Steamboat Springs",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "HLN",
            "answer": "Helena",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "HNL",
            "answer": "Honolulu",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "IAD",
            "answer": "Washington - Dulles",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "IAH",
            "answer": "Houston",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "IDA",
            "answer": "Idaho Falls",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "JFK",
            "answer": "New York - JFK",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "JNU",
            "answer": "Juneau",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "KOA",
            "answer": "Kona",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "KTN",
            "answer": "Ketchikan",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "LAP",
            "answer": "La Paz",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "LAS",
            "answer": "Las Vegas",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "LAX",
            "answer": "Los Angeles",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "LGB",
            "answer": "Long Beach",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "LIH",
            "answer": "Kauai",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "LIR",
            "answer": "Liberia, Costa Rica",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "LTO",
            "answer": "Loreto",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "LWS",
            "answer": "Lewiston",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "MCI",
            "answer": "Kansas City",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "MCO",
            "answer": "Orlando",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "MEX",
            "answer": "Mexico City",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "MFR",
            "answer": "Medford",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "MIA",
            "answer": "Miami",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "MMH",
            "answer": "Mammoth Lakes",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "MRY",
            "answer": "Monterey",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "MSO",
            "answer": "Missoula",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "MSP",
            "answer": "Minneapolis",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "MSY",
            "answer": "New Orleans",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "MZT",
            "answer": "Mazatlan",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "OAK",
            "answer": "Oakland",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "OGG",
            "answer": "Maui",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "OKC",
            "answer": "Oklahoma City",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "OMA",
            "answer": "Omaha",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "OME",
            "answer": "Nome",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "ONT",
            "answer": "Ontario",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "ORD",
            "answer": "Chicago",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "OTZ",
            "answer": "Kotzebue",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "PDX",
            "answer": "Portland",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "PHL",
            "answer": "Philadelphia",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "PHX",
            "answer": "Phoenix",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "PRC",
            "answer": "Prescott",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "PSC",
            "answer": "Pasco",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "PSG",
            "answer": "Petersburg",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "PSP",
            "answer": "Palm Springs",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "PUW",
            "answer": "Pullman",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "PVR",
            "answer": "Puerto Vallarta",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "RDD",
            "answer": "Redding",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "RDM",
            "answer": "Redmond",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "RDU",
            "answer": "Raleigh-Durham",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "RNO",
            "answer": "Reno",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "SAN",
            "answer": "San Diego",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "SAT",
            "answer": "San Antonio",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "SBA",
            "answer": "Santa Barbara",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "SCC",
            "answer": "Prudhoe Bay",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "SEA",
            "answer": "Seattle",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "SFO",
            "answer": "San Francisco",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "SIT",
            "answer": "Sitka",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "SJC",
            "answer": "San Jose",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "SJD",
            "answer": "Los Cabos",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "SJO",
            "answer": "San Jose, Costa Rica",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "SLC",
            "answer": "Salt Lake City",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "SMF",
            "answer": "Sacramento",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "SNA",
            "answer": "Orange County",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "STL",
            "answer": "St Louis",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "STS",
            "answer": "Santa Rosa",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "SUN",
            "answer": "Sun Valley",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "TPA",
            "answer": "Tampa",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "TUS",
            "answer": "Tucson",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "WRG",
            "answer": "Wrangell",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "YAK",
            "answer": "Yakutat",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "YEG",
            "answer": "Edmonton",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "YKM",
            "answer": "Yakima",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "YLW",
            "answer": "Kelowna",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "YVR",
            "answer": "Vancouver",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "YYC",
            "answer": "Calgary",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "YYJ",
            "answer": "Victoria",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "ZIH",
            "answer": "Ixtapa",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "ZLO",
            "answer": "Manzanillo",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "MIL",
            "answer": "Milwaukee",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "HAV",
            "answer": "Havana",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "ICT",
            "answer": "Wichita",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "IND",
            "answer": "Indianapolis",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "SBP",
            "answer": "San Luis Obispo",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "DAL",
            "answer": "Dallas - Love Field",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          },
          {
            "question": "LGA",
            "answer": "New York - LaGuardia",
            "hint": "",
            "category": "Airport Codes"
          }

	]
}]
